这座体育场，什么地方最让你印象深刻？
What stands out to you about this stadium?
你可能会提到它大胆的外立面，或者那顶巨大的顶篷。
You might mention the bold facade or the giant canopy.
如果你是纽约州布法罗的居民，
Or if you're a resident of Buffalo, New York,
大概还会提到——你正在为它出钱买单。
you'll probably mention that you're helping to pay for it.
但如果你是个橄榄球狂热粉丝，你会立刻注意到：
But if you're a football fanatic, you'll instantly notice
这座场馆和其他NFL新球场长得完全不一样。
this looks nothing like any other new NFL stadium.
大胆、炫目，几乎像是来自另一个世界。
Bold, dazzling, almost otherworldly.
而另一边是新海马克——传统、实用，
And then there's New Hark, traditional, utilitarian,
放在50年前的任何美国大城市都毫无违和感。
and seemingly not out of place in any major US city 50 years ago.
虽然这听起来像是在讽刺，但相信我，真的不是。
And while that might sound like the setup for an insult, trust me, it's not.
凭借老派砖墙细节和向自然开放的设计风格，
With its old school brick detailing and open to the element style,
新海马克体育场是一座让人想起昔日经典场馆的建筑。
New Hark Stadium is a facility that hearkens back to the venues of yester year.
问题是：布法罗比尔队为什么要在2026年建一座"过去的体育场"？
The question is, why are the Buffalo Bills building a stadium of the past in 2026?
随着NFL（美国国家橄榄球联盟）的全球影响力持续扩大，你肯定不会惊讶——
With its growing global appeal, you won't be surprised to hear
它是全球盈利能力最强的职业体育联盟。
the NFL is the most financially profitable sports league on the planet.
看看各支球队的估值就知道了。
Just take a look at the value of its franchises.
根据《福布斯》的数据，达拉斯牛仔队
According to Forbes, the Dallas Cowboys top the worldwide polls
以高达130亿美元的估值高居全球榜首。
with a staggering value of $13 billion US.
在这份榜单上，大西洋对岸最接近的足球俱乐部是皇家马德里——
The nearest football or soccer team if you're across the pond
排名第20，估值接近70亿美元。
is the mega giant Real Madrid, which ranks 20th at nearly 7 billion.
前20名中，有13支是NFL球队。
Of the top 20, an impressive 13 are NFL franchises.
前50名里，有30支来自NFL。
And of the top 50, 30 are from the NFL.
而整个NFL联盟只有32支球队。
And there are only 32 teams in the National Football League.
所以，你明白了吧。
So, you get the picture.
这项运动真的是财源滚滚。
The sport really is rolling in money.
但随着这项运动持续飞速发展，
But as the game continues its rapid ascension
全世界的目光也开始更多地投向这项美国国民运动——没错，就是美式橄榄球，别想歪了。
and the eyes of the world start paying more attention to America's game,
no, not that one.
联盟里的各支球队都面临着巨大压力，必须跟上时代的步伐。
Franchises across the league are under heaps of pressure to keep up.
这正是为什么新球场不断涌现。
It's why new stadiums have been popping up left, right, and center.
NFL最新的球场将于2026年夏季开放，这就是新海马克体育场（New Highark），
The league's newest stadium set to open in summer 2026 is New Highark,
布法罗比尔队的未来主场。比尔队目前的主场是联盟中最古老的设施之一——
future home of the Buffalo Bills.
海马克体育场（Highark Stadium）。
The franchise currently plays at one of the oldest facilities in the NFL,
the Highark Stadium.
海马克体育场（Highark Stadium）。
把老球场改造成符合现代要求的场馆，代价极其昂贵。
Renovating it to be ready for the modern day would be extortionate.
举个例子，皇家马德里的球场翻新就花了20亿美元。
Real Madrid's stadium renovation, for example, cost $2 billion.
你看，无论你打算做多大程度的改造，
You see, depending on the amount of work you're doing,
本质上都是在一个老旧的结构骨架上强行植入现代设施。
you're basically merging modern amenities into an old structural skeleton.
而这个骨架本身可能也需要大修。
And that skeleton itself may need a refresh.
所以，从头建一座新球场其实更合算。
So, a brand new stadium kind of made more sense.
不过，也别以为新球场就便宜了。
Although, don't go thinking it comes cheap.
新海马克体育场的造价依然高达令人咋舌的21亿美元。
New Highark still costs an eyewashering $2.1 billion.
作为参照，2020年开放的Allegiant体育场造价约19亿美元。
For context, Allegent, which opened in 2020, cost around $1.9 billion.
2017年开放的梅赛德斯-奔驰体育场约16亿美元；
Mercedes-Benz, which opened in 2017, cost about $1.6 billion.
而SoFi体育场——洛杉矶公羊队和闪电队的主场——造价高达约50亿美元。
And the Sofi Stadium, home to both the Rams and the Chargers, cost around 5 billion.
值得关注的是新海马克庞大的公共资金投入——
What's worth noting is the massive public investment being put towards new Highark,
来自地方和州纳税人、颇具争议的8.5亿美元。
a rather unpopular $850 million thanks to local and state taxpayers.
纳税人真的应该承担这笔账单吗？
Should taxpayers be expected to pick up that kind of a tab?
地方政府和州政府又从哪里筹到这笔钱？
And where would local and state governments come up with that kind of cash?
>> 这是公共资金投入NFL球场有史以来最大的一笔，
>> It's one of the biggest investments ever made by the public into an NFL stadium,
而且它甚至连屋顶都没有。
and it doesn't even have a roof.
支持者的论点是：一座崭新的体育场能为城市创造价值。
The argument is that a fresh new stadium adds value to a city.
从长远来看，它应该能通过吸引球迷、演唱会观众等各类访客
In the long run, it should deliver financial gains
为当地带来经济收益。
by attracting visitors to the area for football matches, gigs,
or whatever else is happening at the stadium.
为当地带来经济收益。
但现实是，研究表明这类投资
But in reality, research suggests that these kind of investments
几乎从来不会给城市居民带来实际的经济收益。
almost never result in economic gains for a city's residents.
对于那些对橄榄球毫无兴趣的纳税人来说，这让人沮丧吗？
Is that frustrating for taxpayers with no interest in football?
当然，绝对是。
Yes, absolutely.
但如果这些计划没有落实，布法罗比尔队就要离开布法罗了。
But until these plans were confirmed, Buffalo Bills were looking to leave Buffalo.
毕竟，近年来已经不止一支球队离开故土，
After all, it wouldn't be the first team in recent memory
迁往所谓更好的城市。
to uproots and make for supposedly greener pastures.
但有了新海马克，比尔队将继续留在布法罗，就像1960年以来一直做的那样。
But now with New Highark, the team will stay in Buffalo as they have since 1960.
就在现有球场对面的停车场上，
In a car park right across the road from the current stadium,
新海马克体育场正在拔地而起。
the new Highark Stadium is now on the rise.
好了，这个周末，NFL赛季就要落幕，
Now, come the weekend, the NFL season will be over
我们将迎来新的超级碗冠军。
and we'll have a new Super Bowl champion.
这是一项需要数年乃至数十年艰苦奋斗
It's a serious accolade that takes years, if not decades,
和长远规划才能赢得的荣誉。
of hard work and forward planning.
但对我们大多数人来说——毕竟不是每个人都能成为职业运动员——
But for the majority of us who will never compete at professional sports,
设定目标同样重要。
it's still really important to have goals.
不管是想在饭桌上多一些有趣的谈资，
Whether it's just to sound more interesting over dinner,
还是想真正弄懂AI对地球意味着什么，今天的视频赞助商Brilliant绝对是你最好的老师。
or you want to finally get to grips with what AI really means for our planet,
there's seriously no better teacher than today's video sponsor, Brilliant.
有了Brilliant，你不只是学到皮毛。
With Brilliant, you don't just come away with the basics.
你能深入理解数学、工程、AI和科学等学科的核心内容。
You earn a deeper understanding of subjects like maths, engineering, AI, and science.
所有内容都通过可视化辅助工具和互动解题的方式呈现，让你真正学进去。
It's all delivered using visual aids and interactive problem solving, so you actually learn.
但说实话，我们都有过这样的经历——
But let's be honest, we've all ended up reaching for our phone
明明要专心做事，结果不是拿起手机，就是盯着窗外看邻居点了什么外卖。
or looking out the window to see what the neighbors order for dinner
when we're meant to be focusing on a task.
但用Brilliant就不会这样。
But that won't happen with Brilliant.
这款应用有研究支撑的学习方式
The app's approach is backed by research
能让我保持专注。
that keeps me focused and on the ball.
比如，如果你以前觉得"我天生不是学数学的料，"
For instance, in the past, if you thought, well, I'm not a maths person.
"我的脑子就是转不过来那个弯。"
my brain just doesn't work that way.
那给自己一个机会，试试Brilliant。
Do yourself a favor and give Brilliant a go.
学习方式真的太重要了。
The way you learn is so important.
有了Brilliant，你不用死记那些枯燥的公式。
And with Brilliant, you don't just memorize
mind-numbing formulas.
你会真正动手实践，直到真正理解那些概念。
You actually get hands-on with concepts until they make sense.
这是一种个性化的、有研究支撑的学习——正在让我成为更好的思考者。
It's personalized, researchedback learning that's making me a better thinker.
我真诚地向你推荐。
And I genuinely can't recommend it highly enough.
但在你去领取30天免费试用之前，
But before you go grabbing your free 30-day trial,
我还需要先告诉你：新海马克体育场为何是NFL里的一个异类。
I first need to tell you why the new Highark Stadium is such an outlier in the NFL.
别担心，
Don't worry, I'm going to be your accountability partner here,
等我们讲完，我会再次提醒你去试试Brilliant。
and I will remind you about Brilliance again once we're done.
我们对现代NFL设施的一切认知，
Now, everything we know from modern NFL facilities
都可以从最近开放的四座球场中获得。
can be learned from the last four most recently opened stadiums.
看看它们吧。
I mean, just look at them.
它们看起来像是复仇者联盟那个不那么秘密的总部。
They look like they could be the not so secret headquarters of the Avengers
or something.
从外观来看，你几乎不会意识到那是橄榄球场。
From the outside, you'd barely know they were football stadiums.
说实话，它们本来也不只是橄榄球场。
And in all honesty, they're not football stadiums.
我是说，它们当然是，但重点是，
I mean, they are, but what I mean is
它们承载的远不止橄榄球这一项功能。
they're about a lot more than just football.
它们是多功能场馆，可以举办演唱会、音乐节、各类赛事，
They're multi-purpose venues built to host concerts, festivals, gigs,
比如摔角狂热大赛，什么都能办。
Wrestlemania, whatever else might be going on.
说白了，它们就是超大号的营销和吸金机器。
Basically, they're really big marketing and cash generating machines.
[笑] 这些球场封闭在极具视觉冲击力的屋顶之下，
[snorts] They're closed to the elements
可以全年使用，不受天气影响。
thanks to these spectacular looking roofs which enable year round usage.
记住，NFL赛季只从九月持续到二月，
Remember, the football season only runs from September to February,
具体取决于你的球队能否打进季后赛。
depending on whether your team makes the playoffs.
橄榄球休赛期间，还有整整六个月的时间可以赚钱。
There's a whole 6 months of money to be made while football takes a break.
它们外覆玻璃，打造出高档质感，
They're clad in glass to create a premium aesthetic,
甚至连草坪都不是真草。
and even the grass isn't really grass.
最近开放的四座球场中，有三座采用了人工草坪，
Three of the four most recently opened stadiums feature an artificial playing surface
因为更容易维护。
because it's easier to maintain.
然后是新海马克体育场——它的设计似乎只围绕一个核心优先级展开。
And then we have New Highark Stadium, seemingly designed with one key priority.
从第一天起，一切都以橄榄球为先——Bills Mafia球迷团，为球队设计，
From day one, it was all about football first, Bill's Mafia, designing for the team,
为球迷设计，我们从未动摇过。
designing for the fans, and we never wavered off of that.
>> 和同类球场相比，这里找不到豪华屋顶、人工草坪，
>> Unlike its peers, you'll find no fancy roof, no artificial playing surface,
也没有奇特的外立面造型。
and no crazy looking exterior facad.
因为极端天气，本就是这里比赛日体验的一部分。
You see, punishing weather is all part of the game day experience here.
>> 这是我这辈子去过的最冷的比赛，没有之一。
>> By far the coldest game I've ever been to in my life.
恶劣天气就像是比尔队名单上额外的一名球员，让对手苦不堪言。
It's kind of the extra player on the build's roster, making life difficult for opposition players.
保留露天设计是球队管理层的核心决策，但同时也配备了一些创新工程方案，
Ownership was key to protect the open air exposure, but critically with some innovative engineering solutions
确保新海马克体育场实际上是一座面向未来的场馆。
to make sure that New Highark is in fact a stadium of the future.
虽然我很确定，省下一大笔屋顶造价这件事，
Although I'm pretty sure that saving millions on a fancy roof probably did play a part
在决策过程中也起了不小的作用。
in the decision-making.
尽管这座球场没有跟随其他新场馆设定的现代潮流，
While this stadium may not be following the modern trends set by other new arenas,
但它的技术确实是面向未来的。
its tech certainly is designed for the future.
就像你比赛日到场的流程一样，让我们从球场外部开始，
Just like you would when arriving for game day, let's start outside the stadium
一路走进去看看。
and work our way in.
在底座部分，铁锈色砖块形成一条厚实的基础腰线，赋予建筑沉稳的气场。
At the base, iron spot bricks form a solid band to give the building a modest grounding.
向上蔓延的竖向元素则传递出一种力量与气势。
Sprawling vertical elements then give a sense of power and strength.
>> 建筑外部主要使用了两种材料。
>> There's two primary materials that we see on the outside of the building.
第一种是步行层的砖砌层，
You know, the first is is the brick coursing at at the pedestrian level,
这与布法罗城市中大量使用砖材的传统一脉相承。
and that ties to a lot of the usage of brick throughout Buffalo.
从某种意义上说，这座城市在历史建筑中本就是一座"砖城"。
In many ways, it was kind of a a brick town in some of the historic architecture.
当你拉开距离，从更远处俯瞰整体设计，
When you kind of zoom out and look at the overall design from further away,
你会注意到金属外立面上有一些凹陷的纹路。
you'll notice these kind of depressions in the metal facade.
这些凹陷在形态上与奥德和克莱因曼音乐厅
Those depressions are essentially akin to the Odd and Kleinman's Music Hall
以及布法罗1939年的一批历史建筑遥相呼应。
and some of the historic 1939 buildings in Buffalo.
现在，我们最想让你看到的，是外立面——也就是建筑"表皮"上的这些东西。
Now, what we really want to show you on that exterior facade or the skin of the building
is these.
它们是球场防御极端天气的第一道独特屏障。
They're the first of a few unique weather deterrents in the armory.
数以千计的穿孔覆盖着外立面上4400块巨型钢板。
Thousands of perforations cover the 4,400 giant steel panels
that span the external facade.
这些穿孔的形状与布法罗比尔队的"冲锋"队徽相同，
Shaped like the Buffalo Bills charge logo, the gaps serve a very special purpose,
用途非常特殊——操控风向。
wind manipulation.
这座球场的设计理念是拥抱自然元素，
While the stadium is designed to embrace the elements, who wants to sit in a freezing bowl,
但谁也不想坐在一个冰冷的碗里，不停地抵御布法罗的寒风，
constantly fending off the cold gusts of Buffalo air,
当风穿过这些穿孔时，会进入孔隙并减速，
as wind hits the perforations, it enters the gaps and slows,
方向也变得混乱。
becoming kind of confused.
这样就阻止了气流翻越球场顶部、在碗型内部循环，
This stops the air flowing over the top of the stadium and circling inside the bowl,
避免了刺骨寒风在比赛日肆虐。
making for a bitter and blustery game day experience.
顺带一说，这不仅仅保护了球迷，
And by the way, that doesn't just protect fans from cold conditions.
还意味着乔什·艾伦可以在几乎没有风阻的情况下把球投向深远区域。
It also means Josh Allen can throw rockets down field with very little wind interference.
但对于了解布法罗冬天的人来说，
But anyone who's been to Buffalo in the winter knows the wind is not
风并不是最严酷的天气挑战。
the most dramatic weather obstacle.
>> 到处都是雪。
>> There's snow everywhere.
>> 布法罗比尔队在一个满是积雪的球场里迎战旧金山49人队。
>> The Buffalo Bills, they face the 49ers in a snowpacked stadium.
>> 就连在奥查德帕克地区，我们的积雪也超过了两英尺。
>> Even in the Orchard uh Park area, we got just over 2 ft of snow.
>> 这座球场从来就不打算建屋顶。
>> This stadium was never going to have a roof.
这支球队，这批球队管理层，他们就是要在布法罗的十二月打橄榄球。
this team, this ownership was all about football in December in Buffalo.
你知道的，下雪其实是一种优势，
And you know, snow is a friend, right, in terms of the of of the,
在主场优势这件事上，雪是朋友。
you know, the home field advantage.
当然，话虽如此，我们还是希望让球迷保持干燥。
Uh, that being said, we wanted to keep the fans dry.
>> 这座城市每年的降雪量约为95英寸，
>> The city experiences about 95 in of snowfall each year,
是整个美国降雪最多的地区之一。
making it one of the snowiest areas in the whole of the US.
虽然大雪是这里比赛日体验的重要组成部分，但它毕竟寒冷、破坏性强、分量沉重，
And while it is a big part of the game day experience here, it's cold, pretty disruptive,
会对结构构件造成损耗。
and heavy, meaning it takes a toll on the structural elements.
这正是新海马克体育场大显身手的地方。
That's where the stadium comes into its own.
在预制混凝土看台中内置了加热系统，让座位区保持温暖，草坪下方也铺设了额外的加热装置；
Alongside heating in the pre-cast concrete stands to keep seating areas warm and further heating underneath the pitch,
而球场顶部的顶篷，远不只是一块钢制遮蔽物那么简单。
the canopy at the top of the stadium is a lot more than just a steel covering.
顶篷从结构框架向外伸展，向下并向内收束，
As it stretches out over the stands from the structural frame, it tapers down and inwards
形成一个漏斗形——有点像一个歪歪斜斜的V字形。
to create a funnel, kind of like a wonky V.
当雪花落下时，传感器感知到温度变化，自动启动——
When snow falls, sensors detect the change in temperature, automatically activating
据马利介绍，这是NFL中规模最大的融雪系统。
what Mali describes as the largest snow melt system in the NFL.
热水通过缠绕在顶篷上的管道输送，
Hot water is sent through pipes that wrap around the canopy to melt the snow as it lands
边融化落雪，边向下方辐射热量。
and in turn radiate heat down below.
这套系统叫做水暖系统。
It's called a hydronic system.
这个顶篷覆盖了约60%的观众席。
That canopy covers around 60% of all fans.
但它还有第二个功能。
But it has a secondary purpose, too.
你看，完全开放式的球场虽然也很嘈杂，但往往会损失一些比赛日的氛围。
You see, completely open air stadiums, while still loud, tend to lose some of the game day experience.
而这个钢制顶篷经过专门设计，以特定角度将声音锁在碗状空间内，
But this steel canopy has been specifically angled to trap noise inside the bowl,
让声波在钢板上反弹、回响，穿透整个看台。
bouncing off the steel and reverberating it back through the stands.
这一切都是为了完成一个使命——打造NFL中最令对手胆寒的主场氛围。
It's all part of this mission to create the most intimidating atmosphere anywhere in the NFL.
新球场的座位容量从旧球场的约7.2万个精简到了6万个，
Seating capacity has been stripped back to 60,000 from about 72,000 at the old stadium
另有5000至1万人可以在纯站立区体验比赛。
with a further 5 to 10,000 people able to experience games from a standing only section.
这一设计理念在于：站立的球迷会制造更多噪音，从而营造出更热烈的氛围。
The idea is that standing fans create more noise leading to a more vibrant atmosphere.
英国顶级联赛的橄榄球和足球球迷，随着新式安全站立区的引入，
Football or soccer fans in the UK at top level fixtures are starting to experience a similar thing
也在重新体验类似的感受。
once again with the introduction of new safe standing areas.
NFL有些球场存在整个角落区域空旷、
There are some stadiums in the NFL where you have like an entire open corner
或者不同座位区域彼此割裂的问题。
or you know there's different seating com sections that are not really connected.
当你拥有连续性，就是在为球迷群体创造凝聚力，
When you have continuity, you're creating continuity for the fan base
而Bills Mafia球迷团就需要这种凝聚力。
and Bill's Mafia wants that.
所以，打造360度环绕式的观赛环境，
So creating that 360° environment creates, you know, this kind of energy amongst the fans
能在球迷之间激发出那种无可比拟的能量。
which is really second to none.
为了让对手更加忌惮，上层看台离球场草坪的距离将是全联盟最近的，
In the interest of making the experience more intimidating for visiting teams, the upper seating deck will be
普通观众席到球场的距离也是全联盟最短的。
the closest to the pitch of any stadium in the league, and it'll feature the closest general admission tickets to the grass.
说我俗气也好——但多年以后，你可能会忘记某场比赛的比分，
Call me cliche, but years down the line, you might forget the score of a particular game,
但你永远不会忘记当时身处其中的那种感受。
but you'll remember the way you felt when you were there.
这正是比尔队想用新海马克体育场去捕捉和创造的东西。
And that is what the Bills are trying to capture and create with the new Highark Stadium.
这座场馆将比NFL中任何一座球场都更亲密、更有临场感。
This venue is going to be more intimate than any other in the NFL.
它让球迷得以离球员更近，听到每一次战术部署，
It's going to enable fans to get closer to the players, to hear each play call,
真切感受到场上的能量。
and really feel the energy of the action on the field.
说到底，这才是现场观看体育赛事的意义所在。
And at the end of the day, that is what being a spectator at a live sports event is all about.
海马克体育场令人印象深刻，但形式服从功能。
The Highark Stadium is impressive, but form follows function.
首先，它是一座橄榄球场。
And first and foremost, this is a football stadium.
它配备了突破性的工程技术，以创新方式应对布法罗的气候挑战，
It's kitted out with groundbreaking engineering, innovative answers to Buffalo's climate,
还被人拿来和某个东西做比较——不过马利对此并不太在意。
and it's been compared to one of these, but Mali isn't too concerned about that.
这很好笑，我现在就在笑——因为我亲身参与过的每一个优秀球场、场馆或项目，
It's funny, and I'm smiling because every great stadium, arena, project that I've personally worked on,
在建成之前总会有各种评论，"看起来像这个"，
there's always been commentary ahead of time before it's built, it looks like this,
"有人说像那个"。
and you know, somebody says it looks like that.
首先，这说明公众在关注它，这本身就是极好的事。
First of all, that's, you know, that's general public great commentary.
它成为了话题。
It's being talked about.
等到观众满场、正式开幕，那些闲话自然烟消云散。
When it's filled and when it opens, all of that will be by the wayside.
我对此充满信心。
I'm fully confident in that.
>> 这些创新之处再怎么令人称道，有一个事实是绕不过去的：
>> As innovative as all of these additions are, there's no getting around to one plain fact.
没有屋顶。
There is no roof.
正如我之前提到的，有了屋顶，你就可以全年举办各种其他活动，而不必担心风雪。
As I mentioned earlier, a roof allows you to host a whole world of other events year round
that snow and rain simply can't be a part of.
尽管新海马克的工程设计令人赞叹，但它本质上是一座拥抱极端天气、而非消除极端天气的场馆。
And as amazing as the engineering behind New Hark is, it's a stadium that's built to embrace the elements
rather than eradicate them.
那么，这座新球场有朝一日能承办橄榄球最大的盛事吗？
So, will this new stadium ever be able to host football's biggest events?
>> 我觉得布法罗嘛，在某些年份可能会有点难。
>> I think Buffalo, you know, in that type of year might be a little bit tough.
永远别说永远。
Uh, never never say never.
要把人们吸引到超级碗这类大型赛事所在的非主要城市，确实是个挑战，但我对此还抱有希望。
Drawing people to non- major, you know, cities and locations for Super Bowl is a little bit of a challenge,
but uh my fingers are crossed.
所以，举办超级碗可能是奢望，但说实话，就像我们已经说清楚的那样，这座球场就是为比尔队球迷而建的。
So hosting the Super Bowl may be a no-go, but if truth be told, as we've already made clear,
this is a venue built for Bill's fans.
钢结构封顶仪式已经完成，工程正进入最后阶段，开幕时间定于2026年夏季。
A topping out ceremony for the steel structure has come and gone with construction moving into the latter stages
ahead of the opening in summer 2026.
当然，我并不是在贬低SoFi或美国银行体育场这样的新场馆——说真的，它们是史诗级的建筑与工程奇迹——但新海马克这座为橄榄球纯粹主义者而建的球场，有种独特的令人满足的感觉。
And without rubbishing some of the new facilities like SoFi and US Bank Stadium because let's be honest,
they are epic, spectacular feats of architecture engineering,
当然，我并不是在贬低SoFi或美国银行体育场这样的新场馆——说真的，它们是史诗级的建筑与工程奇迹——但新海马克这座为橄榄球纯粹主义者而建的球场，有种独特的令人满足的感觉。
there's something quite satisfying about the Highark Stadium being built for football purists.
这个地方看起来将把老球场的精髓与现代技术融为一体，以温柔而细腻的方式，将布法罗比尔队及其历史带向未来。
This place looks like it's set to combine the best of the old stadium with new modern tech
to very gently and delicately bring the Buffalo Bills and its history into the future.
当你走进新海马克，你应该仍然能感受到那种布法罗独有的比赛日氛围，同时又多了几分现代的舒适感。
When you go to New High Mark, you should still get that unique Buffalo game day feeling,
but with more than a touch of modern comfort.
它将提供一种与NFL任何其他新球场都截然不同的体验。
It'll offer a very different experience to any other new stadium in the NFL.
这本身就值得为之喝彩。
And that in itself should be celebrated.
本视频由Brilliant赞助。
This video was sponsored by Brilliant.
别忘了点击下方链接去看看他们。
Don't forget to go and check them out at the link below.
记住，当你们花时间去了解我们的视频赞助商，对我们的频道真的帮助很大。
And remember, it really helps the channel when you guys take the time
to go and check out our video sponsors.
一如既往，如果你喜欢这个视频，想从建筑领域最权威的视频频道获取更多内容，记得订阅B1M。
And as always guys, if you enjoyed this video and you want to get more from the definitive video channel for construction,
make sure you're subscribed to the B1M.